<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>PyNQ.org</title><link href="http://pynq.org/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://pynq.org/feeds/general.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://pynq.org/</id><updated>2012-08-31T00:00:00+10:00</updated><entry><title>Let’s go</title><link href="http://pynq.org/2012/08/lets-go/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2012-08-31T00:00:00+10:00</updated><author><name>davidjb</name></author><id>tag:pynq.org,2012-08-31:2012/08/lets-go/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;So here we have it.  The very first post written for the Python North
Queensland (PyNQ) users group.  If you&amp;#8217;re reading this, it means something
did work or else you&amp;#8217;re in the wrong place. If you&amp;#8217;re looking for one of these
sorts of&amp;nbsp;pythons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="" src="http://pynq.org/images/Python_Snake.jpg" style="height: 200px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="" src="http://pynq.org/images/monty-python.jpg" style="height: 200px;" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;then you&amp;#8217;ll probably be somewhat disappointed.  Typically, the audience
is the sort of person we&amp;#8217;re targetting is the one interested in this sort of&amp;nbsp;Python:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="" src="http://pynq.org/images/python-logo.png" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#8217;s the Python programming language rather than an actual python (see:
snake) or Monty Python (see: humour).  If this makes no sense to you, then
welcome!  You are just the person we&amp;#8217;re looking for to join us.  We do
encourage both snakes and fans of Monty Python to attend, though so don&amp;#8217;t feel
afraid to join us even if you don&amp;#8217;t know what Python programming&amp;nbsp;is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still with me?  Wow, I must have made some&amp;nbsp;impression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At present, this group is in its infancy; a twinkle in the eye, as it were.
The good news is that with just a little interest, and effectively no work on
anyone&amp;#8217;s part, we can manage to make something great happen. If you&amp;#8217;re
interested in meeting up casually to talk about programming, technology, life,
and of course Python, then sing&amp;nbsp;out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At present, the base of operations would be Townsville.  Depending on interest
in the future, we&amp;#8217;ll certainly look at expanding to Cairns and possibly other
centres.  I&amp;#8217;m unsure just how many Pythonistas are out in Mount Isa or Emerald,
but if you&amp;#8217;re out there, don&amp;#8217;t be&amp;nbsp;shy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, we&amp;#8217;re gathering interest, so ping me, David, on &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://twitter.com/davidjb_"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://git.io/djb"&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and express
your existence! We&amp;#8217;re North Queensland-based &amp;#8212; that&amp;#8217;s Australia, by the way,
in case you&amp;#8217;re really, really&amp;nbsp;lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#8217;re a coder in Cooktown or Cairns or a technologist in Townsville or
Tully and you work with Python, open source, or other fun loosely-related
(heck, it doesn&amp;#8217;t even need to be related!), then sing out and let&amp;#8217;s meet up on
a semi-regular basis. We can even do something video-conference related if you
can&amp;#8217;t travel the&amp;nbsp;distance.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary></entry></feed>